Fish
魚、
Fish fish fish fish fish fish
魚、魚、魚、魚、魚、魚、本当に
They taste really good
美味しいよ。
I think I want to eat more
もっと食べたい。
They really do taste good
本当に美味しいよ。
Wow-wow
わお。
Fish fish fish fish fish fish
魚、魚、魚、魚、魚、魚、本当に美味しいよ。
They taste really good
本当においしいです
I'm feeling full now,
もうお腹いっぱい。
I'll eat more tomorrow
明日もっと食べる。
Fish fish fish fish fish fish
魚、魚、魚、魚、魚、魚、本当に
They taste really good
美味しいよ。もっと
I think I want to eat more
食べたい。
They really do taste good
本当に美味しいよ。
Wow-wow
わお。
"Jon what the heck is with these lyrics"
「ジョン、この歌詞は一体何なんだ」「
"IM SORRY, 14 yr old me wrote this song"
ごめん、14歳の自分が書いた曲なんだ」「
I'm feeling full now,
もうお腹いっぱい。
I'll eat more tomorrow
明日もっと食べる。」
*dying jon noises*
ジョンの死にそうな声*
jon pls stop
ジョン、お願い、やめて。
r u ok ??
大丈夫？？
*Jon dying inside*
*ジョン、心の中で死にそう*
Do you approve of how you are feeling at this current moment?
あなたは今の自分の気持ちに納得していますか? 魚が
I eat fish everyday until they eat me
私を食べるまで、私は毎日魚を食べます。
Me too.
私もです。